lazymeal.com 2015-07-19

# Privacy

## Data Collection

lazymeal collects certain personal, psychographic and demographic information for the purpose of enhancing your experience. Because your privacy is important to us, please read the measures below to learn about the information lazymeal collects and how it is used and managed. 

## What information does lazymeal collect?

### Personally Identifiable Information

lazymeal may collect various information to process your meal orders, all of which is classified as "Personally Identifiable Information". This may include:

  * your first and last name;
  * street address (including cross streets), city, province, zip code;
  * phone number;
  * email address;
  * GPS location if the meal order is placed via mobile site;
  * credit card information (more info below).

### Demographics Data

Demographics data collected via web analytics software may be disclosed for lazymeal's promotion and marketing purposes. Please note that Personally Identifiable Information will not be shared with third parties should lazymeal choose to publish statistics and findings.

### History on lazymeal

lazymeal may also collect information concerning your history of meal orders via lazymeal. This may include information regarding past meal orders, previous customer concerns, reviews and social network choices including recommended, liked or followed pages while on the lazymeal website.

## How does lazymeal Manage and Use your Information?

### Special Offers and Promotions

lazymeal uses Personally Identifiable Information to process meal orders, extend promotions, special offers, and enhance your overall experience. lazymeal allows you to unsubscribe from all its promotional material.

### Storage of Credit Card Information

lazymeal allows you to (optionally) store addresses and credit card details to make the meal order process more convenient.

#### lazymeal never stores your complete credit card number or pin-code

Even in the unlikely event of a security breach of our servers, your credit card info could not be stolen. Only our credit card processing partner stores your full credit card info, on their high-security servers.

### Cookies

Cookies are used by lazymeal to remember your preferences in order to optimize your experience. Cookies allow lazymeal to store previously used addresses, and if you chose to do so, can automatically log you in.

We might also use cookies to display Advertisements on third party websites via Google Networks. This is done based on the history of your visits to lazymeal.com. You can opt out of third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

### Information from User Generated Content

Because of the public nature of the lazymeal blog, reviews and integration of social networks, lazymeal cannot account for the privacy of Personally Identifiable Information in user generated content.

### lazymeal Web Security

lazymeal uses secure protocols that are widely recognized and used. However, lazymeal cannot guarantee the security of Personally Identifiable Information. lazymeal users partake in web ordering at their own risk.

## How Can you Change or Restrict Information Shared with lazymeal?

Log-in to your lazymeal user account to change your shared Personally Identifiable Information as desired. If you have further concerns regarding your privacy and information, please contact [info@lazymeal.com](mailto:info@lazymeal.com) and a lazymeal representative will respond within 48 hours.

## lazymeal Privacy Policy Terms

lazymeal reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by editing this page. The new Privacy Policy is effective upon an immediate update of this page.
